<?xml version="1.0"?>
<extension key="org.civicrm.civirebux" type="module">
  <file>civirebux</file>
  <downloadUrl>https://github.com/ypranay/org.civicrm.civirebux/archive/v1.0.zip</downloadUrl>
  <name>CiviREBUX</name>
  <description>A native CiviCRM extension for drafting custom Contribution and Membership reports via a drag-n-drop interface. CiviREBUX combines powerful visualization and transformation techniques which gives users full capabilities of modern browsers and freedom to design the right elements for their reports. CiviREBUX also supports saving and loading of report templates for later use. If you are using CiviCRM for handling your organizational needs for CRM, CiviREBUX integrates seamlessly within your CiviCRM Dashboard and goes live seconds after installing the extension. CiviREBUX is a mix of the most popular desktop-based spreadsheet software and fast browser applications - essentially, a spreadsheet software running on your browser.</description>
  <urls>
    <url desc="Main Extension Page">https://github.com/ypranay/org.civicrm.civirebux</url>
    <url desc="Documentation">https://github.com/ypranay/org.civicrm.civirebux/wiki</url>
    <url desc="Licensing">http://www.gnu.org/licenses/agpl-3.0.html</url>
    <url desc="Support">https://forum.civicrm.org/index.php?topic=37100.0</url>
  </urls>
  <license>AGPL-3.0</license>
  <maintainer>
    <author>ypranay</author>
    <email>y.pranay@gmail.com</email>
  </maintainer>
  <releaseDate>2016-08-16</releaseDate>
  <version>1.0</version>
  <develStage>stable</develStage>
  <compatibility>
    <ver>4.7</ver>
  </compatibility>
  <comments>This extension was built as a part of Google Summer of Code 2016 by Pranay Yadav, a final year Computer Science student at Indian Insitute of Technology Kharagpur, under the mentorship of Brian Shaughnessy and Jaap Jansma. It is a native extension and tested for compatibility with CiviCRM 4.7.</comments>
  <civix>
    <namespace>CRM/Civirebux</namespace>
  </civix>
</extension>
